Guide to the Carl and Shelley Smith Mydans Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1930-1992; Series I; 33.83; (106 boxes)
  - Slides
    - Housed in Slide Boxes
      - Summer: scenes at Coney Island, New York (For Time), No. 1, 1977 June 22 (Box 69)
      - Con Edison Indian Point Power Plant, Verblank, New York, 1977 July 14 (Box 69)
      - Ocean Park, Hong Kong
        - Macaw and cockatoo show, undated (Box 69)
        - Garden Theatre, undated (Box 69)
        - Performing dolphins and sea lions at Ocean Theatre, 1977 (Box 69)
        - Wave Cove, 1977 (Box 69)
        - Ocean Theatre, 1977 (Box 69)
        - Cable Cars, undated (Box 69)
        - This box was sorted out by Time as selects for story - never used, undated (Box 69)
      - Paul Charlap's helicopter and environs, Larchmont, 1978 July 9 (Box 69)
      - China 1978
        Slides from Mydans' trip to China on the Lindblad Explorer. Includes slides of Japan.
        - Gunther Les and others in flight from Los Angeles to Tokyo, 1978 August (Box 69)
        - Lectures on Lindblad Explorer; Scenes Yokohama, 1978 (Box 69)
        - Lindblad, 1978; (3 slide boxes) (Box 69)
        - Yokohama; scenes on Lindblad Explorer; sunsets, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Moon over Inland Sea, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Mass tourist dinner at Nagasaki, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Mass tourist sukiyaki dinner in Tokyo, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Nagasaki: Scenes at lunch on Lindblad Exp.; scenes departing Nagasaki, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Nagasaki Departure scenes down the bay for China, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Nagasaki Japanese Navy; scenes from hill, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Scenes leaving Nagasaki; also Lars Lindblad, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Inland Sea Nagasaki and fishing craft, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Inland Sea; Mike Demarest against the light, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Shimonoseki: scenes of Shimonoseki Strait, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Japan coast -- Inland Sea, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Coast off Quemoy, 1978 September; (3 slide boxes) (Box 69)
        - Kuei-lin, on the road from Kuei-lin to Li River -- mostly from the bus, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Kuei-lin scenes -- various, from bus and others, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Sunrise over Kuei-lin, Prime, 1978 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 69)
        - Kuei-lin: Reed Flute caves, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Kuei-lin-Li River scenes along Li River: No. 1 - No. 4, 1978 September; (4 slide boxes) (Box 69)
        - View of Kuei-lin, late afternoon from 230 meters "Piled Silk Hill", 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Kuei-lin Scenic pond near entrance to Reed Flute cave, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Kuei-lin Factory workers flat - Tsao Hong-Chi family, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Kuei-lin: on road to Li River; roadside scenes from bus, etc., 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Kuei-lin: general scenes, 1978 September (Box 69)
        - Kuei-lin Acrobatic Troupe, 1978 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 70)
        - Kuei-lin Zoo. Note: Roll 117, normal; Roll 1965 pushed by Eastman from ASA 400 exposed at Asa 64 on frames means pushed film, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Train, Shanghai to Wusih. Through the closed plate glass windows of train, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Wusih figurine factory. Largely portraits. Good pic, mother and babies, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Wusih Workers Convalescent Home, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Wusih: Silk worm breeding, Wusih Commune; also Leave Your Pleasure Park, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Wusih scenes; mother and baby in crowd reacting to us, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Wusih Antique shop. Shelley buying scrolls; Wusih Convalescent Hospital, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Scenes from the bus, Wusih region, and scenes afoot, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Great Wall, 1978 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 70)
        - Tiger Hill, Soochow; tourist take pic of pagoda; etc.; Grand Canal, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Soochow sandalwood fan factory; street scenes, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Soochow: scenes Soochow; Embroidery Research Institute, 1978 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 70)
        - Soochow "West Garden" Buddhist Temple, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Soochow scenes; Richard Jones takes polaroid of child, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Soochow. Street scenes; restaurant; open street shops, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Early morning street scenes, Soochow; Wellington Lee sister and granddaughter (U.N. NY); morning along street and canal, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Road to Peking scenes; Peking Airport, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Peking Airport; tourist picture at airport, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Peking scenes from bus on way to Great Wall, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Peking Forbidden City: Tiananmen Square, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Peking; Forbidden City; Mike Demarest, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Peking, Tiananmen Square; from Great Wall; from bus; bound feet, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Forbidden City; soldiers and horse of Chin Tomb, etc., 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai Concert Hall, concert, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai Children's Palace: stage performance to entertain foreigners, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai street scenes, 1978 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 70)
        - Shanghai Arts and Crafts Research Institute, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai Jade Buddha Temple, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai good tourist pic; new apartment housing; Nanking (?) Road, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai: Bund from Peace Hotel; Old Palace Hotel, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai: tour leaders and red flags, Carey Lindblad and Allen Ricket; from bus: bund, etc., 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai departure, downriver scenes, steel mills, pollution, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai: The Wangpoo -- Sunrise and other views of the river; junks, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai: Waving children, Children's Palace, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai: Junks and river scenes from Lindblad Explorer at Shanghai, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai street scenes, etc.; Shanghai book store (Shelley) also general store, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai Friendship store. Tourists shop and buy, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai: Views of Shanghai skyline on arrival; junks, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai: Peace Hotel, street scenes, 1978 September (Box 70)
        - Shanghai T'ai Chi Ch'uan, morning on the Bund, 1978 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 70)
        - Shanghai Commune, canal boats, machine shop, farmers, acupuncture on commune, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Shanghai: Lindblad Explorer leaves Shanghai pier; scenes down river to Hong Kong, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Shanghai skyline; junks on very hazy morning; also Lindblad Explorer at Hongkew Dock, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Shanghai skyline and river scenes from Lindblad Explorer, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Shanghai, Skyline and river scenes, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Shanghai book store - Shelley, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Shanghai Historical Museum, with 2 soldiers & horse from Sian Chin She Huang tomb; Shanghai department store, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Shanghai Children's Palace, 1978 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - Commune home at Fusame near Canton. ASA rating on FM slipped from 400 to 100 and roll is 2 stops under. (Box 71)
        - Canton: overview of Shwang Ching St. (Two Well St.) Morning views: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1978 September; (4 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - Canton: little streets near Shang Ching Street, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Canton: street scenes, 1978 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - Canton: roadside views from bus, Canton from "Five Story Museum" scenes inside, 1978 (Box 71)
        - Canton: song and dance performance, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Canton: Excursion cruise down Pearl River in poor weather; pollutions, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Canton-Farming: Commune farms just outside Canton, 1978 September; (3 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - Foshan Commune (near Canton), 1978 September; (5 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - Foshan Taoist Temple, 1978 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - Farming, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Bicycles, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Industry and port, 1978 December 18 (Box 71)
        - China, 1978 (Box 71)
        - China: Tourism, 1978 September (Box 71)
        - Numbered frames weeded from drums edited from Time for Simon and Schuster showing 1 (1-2), 1978 November; (2 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - 23 frames already converted by Time, and chosen for the book in black and white, 1978 December 19 (Box 71)
        - 128 frames for conversion and one 8 x 10 print, undated; (3 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - These are the 64 dupes of the lost China Book color. Not for publication, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - Dupes on China; color, used in Time, 1978; (2 slide boxes) (Box 71)
        - Red Circle primes weeded form first carousel selection: No. 1 - No. 4 (1-4), undated; (4 slide boxes) (Box 72)
        - Cover suggestions, 11 frames, 1978 (Box 72)
        - China Book: Nine frames of the frames given S&S for book and not used, and returned to me Nov. 8 1979 (Box 72)
        - Set chosen for Time Ad Sales Presentation: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 72)
        - General dupes on China; color, used in Time, 1978 (Box 72)
      - Pre-publication breakfast for rebirth of LOOK, 1978 October 5 (Box 72)
      - Mexico: West coast
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo: No. 1, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo: No. 2, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo: No. 3, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo: No. 4, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo: pool and beach: No. 5, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo, from boat: No. 6, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo, from boat: No. 7, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo: No. 8, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, General and breakfast scenes etc.: No. 9, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo; Breakfast and from the boat: No. 10, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo; Beach, long views, Club Maeda: No. 11, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Hadas, Manzanillo; Nick and Donna and Shelley Muscoddaly in Safari Jeep: No. 12, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Boat trip from Puerto Vallarta to Yelapa; also pool at Posada Vallarta: No. 13, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Boat trip from Puerto Vallarta to Yelapa: No. 14, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Boat trip: Puerto Vallarta to Yelapa: boat and island scenes: No. 15, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Yelapa Island: No. 16, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Downtown Puerto Vallarta: No. 17, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Downtown Puerto Vallarta: No. 18, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Puerto Vallarta; artist Manuel Lepe; Lupe Dress Shop: No. 19, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Downtown Puerto Vallarta Sunday: No. 22, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Puerto Vallarta downtown - Sunday: No. 23, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Puerto Vallarta beach scenes: No. 24, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Puerto Vallarta: beach and downtown: No. 25, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Puerto Vallarta: downtown; beach and pool at Hotel Posada Vallarta: No. 26, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Puerto Vallarta: downtown; beach and pool at Hotel Posada Vallarta: No. 27, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Parachutes on Beach at Posada Vallarta: No. 28, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Acapulco: beach and breakfast scenes: No. 29, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Acapulco: Villa Vera: No. 30, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Acapulco: general and beach scenes: No. 31, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Acapulco: Las Brisas: No. 32, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Acapulco: Princes Hotel: No. 33, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Acapulco: Princes Hotel; Parachutes: No. 34, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Beach at Hotel Rivera Del Sol at Ixtapa: No. 35, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Zihuatanejo: No. 36, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Zihuatanejo: No. 37, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Fishing boats come in with catch at Zihuatanejo: No. 38, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - Las Gatos (Zihuatanejo): No. 39, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - View of the beach at Rivera del Sol (Lady over-looking): No. 40, 1979 July (Box 72)
        - From Hillside over-looking beach at Rivera Del Sol: No. 41, 1979 July (Box 73)
        - Beach at Hotel Rivera Del Sol at Ixtapa: No. 43, 1979 July (Box 73)
        - Acapulco: Disco: No. 1 - No. 2, 1979 July; (2 slide boxes) (Box 73)
        - Puerto Vallarta Market Place, 1979 July (Box 73)
        - Puerto Vallarta: "Studio Zoo" shop. Roll bounced and under. A few frames copied and intensified, undated (Box 73)
        - Rita's at Yelapa Island Puerto Vallarta; breakfast at Las Hadas, Manzanillo, 1979 July (Box 73)
        - Taxco El Viejo, Acapulco; Old Oceana Bar, Puerto Vallarta; Viva Shop, Puerto Vallarta, 1979 July (Box 73)
        - Mexico, 1979 August (Box 73)
      - Main Room, Kennedy Airport, 1979 September (Box 73)
      - Solar Collector, John Worth Home, near Utica Airport on Route 69, 1979 September 23 (Box 73)
      - San Francisco, California
        - No. 1 - No. 8, 1979 October; (8 slide boxes) (Box 73)
        - Side-bars: No. 1 - No. 2, 1979 October; (2 slide boxes) (Box 73)
        - Fisherman's Wharf, 1979 October (Box 73)
        - From Coit Tower through glass with some reflections, 1979 October (Box 73)
        - Skyline from ferry: No. 1, 1979 October (Box 73)
        - Skyline from the Ferry: No. 1, 1979 October (Box 73)
        - From Transamerica Corp pyramid, 1979 October (Box 73)
        - San Francisco [empty], 1979 October; (3 slide boxes) (Box 73)
      - Pope: NYC, Side-bar scenes around St. Patricks, 1979 October 2 (Box 73)
      - Christmas in Nation's Capitals, Nelson Rockefeller Mall, Albany, New York, 1979 December; (3 slide boxes) (Box 73)
      - Slides for ASMP presentation, 1980 March-April; (8 slide boxes) (Box 73)
        Includes slides of Soviet Union, Britain, Coal & Sandhogs, Korean War, China, and France & Indochina.
      - Photojournalism Presentation, 1980 March-September; (9 slide boxes) (Box 74)
      - Paul Charlap Helicopter Test, 1980 May 31 (Box 74)
      - Convention, The Boston Globe and Curtis Wilkie, 1980 August (Box 74)
      - Convention, 1980 August (Box 74)
      - Carl Mydans' portrait by Eddie Adams, Democratic Convention, New York, 1980 (Box 74)
      - Election Night at the Nightly News desk of NBC, 1980 November 11; (2 slide boxes) (Box 74)
      - OTB Betting Center: 50th between 7th and 8th avenue, 1980 December 10; (2 slide boxes) (Box 74)
      - Pittsburgh, 1981 January (Box 74)
      - China 1981
        - Shanghai: originals and dupes, 9 of which offered N. Geo. by T-Life Agency, 1981 January (Box 74)
        - Ming Tombs, 1981 March (Box 74)
        - Panam: scenes near Ming Tombs; also Lama Temple - the "Yuan He" temple -- Peking, 1981 March (Box 74)
        - (Panam) Peking, 1981 (Box 74)
        - Beijing: early morning scenes along Chang'an Avenue, 1981 March (Box 74)
        - Beijing: State Market -- The Chong Wenmen Food Market Southwest Peking near the Old Gate, 1981 March (Box 74)
        - Beijing: early street scenes on rising sun, along Chang'an Ave, 1981 March (Box 74)
        - Beijing: Sunrise over Chang'an Avenue, 1981 March (Box 74)
        - Peking: Lama Temple; the Yuan He Temple, just reopened after Cul. Revolution, 1981 March; (2 slide boxes) (Box 74)
        - Peking: Street Scenes, 1981 March; (3 slide boxes) (Box 74)
        - Peking: Temple of Heaven; Listening Wall, 1981 March (Box 74)
        - Peking: Tien Chao Theatre, 1981 March (Box 74)
        - Peking Man Cave, China, 1981 March; (4 slide boxes) (Box 74)
        - The Great Wall and adjacent scenes; Ming Tombs; Trans-Siberian Train, 1981 March (Box 74)
        - Great Wall of China, undated (Box 74)
      - Boat Races on the Exeter River, New Hampshire, 1981 May 15 (Box 74)
      - London, England
        - Hampstead and Hampstead Heath, 1981 August (Box 74)
        - Heathwood and the Bull & Bush, 1981 August (Box 74)
        - London Underground, 1981 August 28 (Box 74)
        - Nature's Colors (London Walls), 1981 August (Box 74)
      - Korea
        - Korean prints, photographed at Expo 1970 opening, 1970 March; (3 slide boxes) (Box 75)
        - 100th anniversary of American/Korean relations, Seoul, 1982 May (Box 75)
          Includes slides of Korea House luncheon.
        - Seoul-General Scenes, 1982 May (Box 75)
        - Services, American Cemetery (Foreign Cemetery), Seoul, 1982 May (Box 75)
        - Modern Dance, Folk Art at Korea House, Seoul, 1982 May (Box 75)
        - Panmunjom, The DMZ, 1982 May 25 (Box 75)
        - Ship building, Hyundai Ship Yards, Ulsan, 1982 June (Box 75)
        - Bukug Temple in the Gyeongju Area, 1982 June (Box 75)
        - Rice, No. 1 - No. 4, 1982 June; (4 slide boxes) (Box 75)
      - Bird carvings by Howard Sloan, 1982 December 4 (Box 75)
      - Great Storm waves at Mendocino, California, 1983 February 13 (Box 75)
      - The Bridge at Chappaquiddick, 1983 July 24 (Box 75)
      - Frank Lloyd Wright, furniture at Cooper-Hewitt Museum, 1983 August 31; (4 slide boxes) (Box 75)
      - Turkey
        - Sultan Teppe, Turkey, 1983 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 75)
        - Village near Sultan Teppe, Turkey, 1983 September (Box 75)
        - Urfa, Turkey, 1983 September 24 (Box 75)
        - Fethi Ahmed Pasha Yali and Prof. Eldem, undated (Box 75)
        - Ancient monument stones used for stone fences, Ankara, 1983 September (Box 75)
        - Diyarbakir, Turkey, 1983 September 25; (2 slide boxes) (Box 75)
        - Threshing, farming, Diyarbakir village, 1983 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 75)
        - Watermelons: Diyarbakir, Turkey, 1983 September 25; (2 slide boxes) (Box 75)
        - Yali: Istanbul, 1983 September; (5 slide boxes) (Box 75)
        - Yali: Istanbul with Emel Uygur, 1983 October 1; (8 slide boxes) (Box 75)
        - Bosphorus - Istanbul from Etat Marmara; also sunrise, 1983 October (Box 76)
        - Yali: exteriors we photograph inside, 1983 October (Box 76)
        - Yali scenes from hire boat, 1983 October (Box 76)
        - Yali: interior of the Sabullh Pasha Yali with huge curved ceiling, 1983 October 2 (Box 76)
        - Yali: Istanbul; the Countess Ostrorog Yali, interiors and exteriors, 1983 October 3 (Box 76)
        - Yali: The Rasim Pasha Yali (last we photographed -- in decay), 1983 October 4 (Box 76)
        - Yali scenes from ferry, 1983 October (Box 76)
        - Yalis of the Bosphorus, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 76)
        - Yali: weeded from selects, 1983 October; (4 slide boxes) (Box 76)
      - Grenada, Secretary George Schultz visit, 1984 February 7; (4 slide boxes) (Box 76)
      - Carl Mydans by Bernard Diedrich, Grenada, 1984 February (Box 76)
      - Scribners, Fifth Avenue, NYC, 1984 April 26 (Box 76)
      - Billy Graham, Russia
        - Arrival press conference at the Moscow airport, 1984 September 9 (Box 76)
        - Leningrad; The Piskariovksoye Memorial Cemetery, 1984 September 10 (Box 76)
        - Leningrad Baptist Church, 1984 September 10 (Box 76)
        - Leningrad, the Baptist Church, 1984 September 10 (Box 76)
        - Synagogue in Leningrad, 1984 September 10; (2 slide boxes) (Box 76)
        - Orthodox Theological Seminary in Leningrad, 1984 September 11 (Box 76)
        - Billy Graham: meeting with the Leningrad Peace Committee at the former Schuvalor Pl Place in Leningrad, 1984 September 11 (Box 76)
        - USSR: Tallinn (Billy Graham); possible cat and red door picture, 1984 September 11-12; (3 slide boxes) (Box 76)
        - Moscow: Room 205 National Hotel, 1984 September (Box 76)
        - Moscow Scenes, 1984 September (Box 76)
        - Moscow at the Baptist Church where found Baptist had asked we be barred. Milling press and photographers, 1984 September 15 (Box 76)
        - Service for the Dead: Orthodox Church for the Immaculate Conception, Sokolniki, Moscow (Billy Graham), 1984 September 16 (Box 76)
        - Church of the Immaculate Conception Moscow, 1984 September 16; (3 slide boxes) (Box 76)
        - Billy Graham at "State Office of Religious Affairs and Soviet Peace" Novosibirsk; with Franklin Graham and close-up of Walter Smyth, 1984 September 18 (Box 76)
        - Evangelical Christian Baptist Church at Novosibirsk, 1984 September 18; (3 slide boxes) (Box 76)
        - Orthodox Cathedral, Novosibirsk, 1984 September 19; (9 slide boxes) (Box 77)
          Includes slides of Archbishop Gideon.
        - Christianity in the Soviet Union (These are choices deleted from the two drums chosen to show TIME), 1985 March 11 (Box 77)
        - Orthodox Services, Novosibirsk; used in Time, 1988 April 4 (Box 77)
      - Amon Carter Museum, 1985 July 16; (2 slide boxes) (Box 77)
      - Hanging of pictures at Boston University Art Gallery, 1985 September 17 (Box 77)
      - Floods: California, with Sacramento people at Linda, California, 1986 February 23; (2 slide boxes) (Box 77)
      - Philippine Elections
        - Senator Lorenzo M. Tanada, Arturo M. Tolentino, Manila, 1986 January 29 (Box 77)
        - Cory Aquino in her home in Manila as elections near their end, 1986 February 3; (2 slide boxes) (Box 77)
        - President Marcos and family on election day. Also at Lunetta Rally: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), February 7; (2 slide boxes) (Box 77)
        - Services at the Baclaran Church in Manila with Cory Aquino for the murdered former governor of Antique, Evelio Javier, 1986 February 13 (Box 77)
        - Marcos Elections, 1986 February; (3 slide boxes) (Box 77)
        - Marcos Elections: No. 1 - No. 5, 1986; (5 slide boxes) (Box 77)
        - 4 and 5 frames Philippines elections: No. 1 - No. 10, 1986; (10 slide boxes) (Box 77)
        - Personalities: Tolentino; Cardinal Sin; Laurel Ongpin; Tanada: No. 1 - No. 2, 1986; (2 slide boxes) (Box 77)
        - Tolentino and Tanada current personalities in the conflict, 1986 July (Box 78)
        - Marcos-Imelda: Honolulu, 1986 April 16 (Box 78)
        - Carl, Seth, Luke; Philippines Elections, 1986 (Box 78)
        - Philippines: of me, Seth, Luke, and fellow photographers covering the February elections in PI in 1986 by Tuchi, Moyers and others (Box 78)
        - Three frames, 2 duplicates of these taken by Eleanor Taylor of Picture Week for arthritis story, 1986 September 3 (Box 78)
        - Six frames for Time Year-end issue, undated (Box 78)
        - Philippines Elections, sent to Robin Moyers for "28 Days" book and returned, undated (Box 78)
        - Philippines Elections: special dupes of selected frames remade for quality (5 frames), 1986 (Box 78)
        - Marcos and Imelda -- Honolulu, dupes chosen by Julia Richer for Time, 1987 March 10 (Box 78)
        - 24 frames of Imelda in Honolulu chosen for Eleanor Taylor of Time-- all returned, 1988 (Box 78)
        - Philippines: 5 frames used in book, undated (Box 78)
      - Philippine Elections -- Originals
        - Shelley and Luke at Ft. Santiago: old historic cars etc., 1986 January 28 (Box 78)
        - Senator Lorenzo M. Tanada, leading leftist lawyer in his Manila office, No. 1 - No. 2, 1986 January 29; (2 slide boxes) (Box 78)
        - Street scenes and electioneering posters in Manila near Plaza Miranda, 1986 January 29 (Box 78)